We are pleased to bring you another installment from Gero, this time with the help of the Yukaiki Resort Gero Longest Raku.
It has begun. Team Shachi no Hajime Gaku!
Yay!
This time, too, we will send you four members.
We are all here, in uniform.
We are all here at last!
What a strange feeling.
Since we had two days this time, each day had a different main pair,
On the first day, the Haru and Yuzuke pair was the one to do the vomiting,
Where did Hou-chan and Nao go?
We went to Takayama.
We went there.
We ate and did a lot of things.
I'll see you at a different place.
I was looking forward to seeing the souvenirs.
I'm so happy!
Since you are going to stay overnight on location, what you are interested in is the accommodation, isn't it?
The lodging.
Yes, it is.
It's important, isn't it?
The inn, isn't it?
It's important.
This time, the inn where we will stay is here.
Ta-da!
It's the YUKAI RESORT GERO NAGARAKU SAN!
It's the main building!
Really.
Let's have fun!
I'm going in right away!
I'm off!
Good night!
Kim Kwon Kwon Kwon
Nice to meet you!
Thank you for having us today, we are SENO
Super Turn Strong Energy Positive Exciting Soul
From Nagoya Seam Chassis
Pleased to meet you
Thank you very much for having us.
Thank you very much
I'm glad to be in such a nice place
I'm...
I'm Ei, the manager of Yucai Resort Gero Nagaraku Honkan.
I'm Manager Naga of the Yucai Resort Gero Nagaraku Honkan.
Pleased to meet you.
Please, come this way, please.
Pleasure to meet you.
Great!
I'm off.
I'm off!
Please tell us about your resort, Gero-Nanenraku Honkan.
Please tell us about the Yukai Resort Gero Naga Naga Honkan.
Do you have any special features of your inn?
Our inn is located on a hill, so you can enjoy a beautiful view of the hot spring resort from the baths and restaurant.
The city of Gero spreads out below us.
You can see the mountains of Taira during the day and the beautiful night view at night.
The weather is beautiful today, so I'm sure I'll be back to enjoy the beautiful night view!
There is also a gassho village and a hot spring town with footbaths in the vicinity.
There are also a Gassho Village and a hot spring town with footbaths in the vicinity, so there is plenty to see and do in the area!
Wonderful!
You can enjoy a lot!
You can also enjoy the nature.
There's a bus right in front of you.
Is it easy to get to from Nagoya?
Yes, there is a round-trip bus that goes directly to Nagoya.
Direct?
We have a plan that allows you to use the bus at a reasonable price.
I hope it's easy to get to.
I saw yukata at Aichi Prefecture Suga.
Can we choose a yukata?
We let our guests choose the one they like best.
They're cute!
May I take a look?
Please.
Thank you very much.
Isn't this one?
There are so many kinds.
Which one do you want?
This one's cute.
This one, isn't it?
Napi, is this not the one?Napi, isn't this it?
Already.
I see.
Napi.
Pink.
Perfect.
Hey, Napi.
I remember when yukata dresses were all the rage.
If you have this size
Napi's Yukata Dress
Only one yukata dress
It's a child's size
I wonder which one is for Mom.
Me or Mama
That's Mommy!
That's your mom!
Yutsuki, you're gonna do it!
It looks so good on you.
It looks good.
Let's change her hair.
Part your bangs.
A little bit like this.
I don't know.
I don't think it's a good idea to have a kid's kiss.
I think it's totally fine.
I don't know.
That's cool.
No, it's not.
It's just a dress or something.
Okay, I'm going to go change.
Okay.
I'm going to go get changed.
Enjoy.
There you go!
I've changed.
So cute!
Hidairyuu!
Wait a minute.
There's someone else here.
Now that you're dressed...
Let's go have a nice dinner
Let's go eat a delicious meal together.
It's a buffet.
I want to do it.
I'll be going.
I'm Chef Tsugu.
Mr. Tsugu!
Pleased to meet you.
There's a nice aroma spreading around,
Yes.
What do you recommend?
From March 1 to July 2, we are holding a limited time truffle fair.
Truffle Fair is open for a limited time from March 1 to July 2.
It's a truffle fair!
Truffle hot pot with cream sauce and
This one has a truffle
Cutie pizza!
It's a truffle pizza!
Potato pizza looks delicious!
Pizza! Pizza!
Pizza!
Looks good!
Here we have Takayama Ramen.
It is a local specialty.
Local specialty!
Takayama Ramen!
Local specialties are always good, aren't they?
There are so many.
There are more!
There's sushi, too!
I can see sushi too!
It's truffle sushi.
Because it will be truffle sushi.
Truffle salmon roll sushi.
Truffle sushi?
It's very popular.
It's amazing!
You have to get it!I have to get it!
I'll eat it!
This is the best recommendation.
Aromatic truffle sauce.
Yongenton pork steak with aromatic truffle sauce.
Steak!
Grilled right in front of you.
I see!
Hardened!
This is also with tempura.
There's so much tempura!
There's so much!
There are shrimp, too!
Amazing!
From seasonal items to specialties.
Truffles galore!
From seafood to meat!
So many!
I'm starving!
I can't wait to eat!
Shall we go?
Let's go!
Thank you very much!
Next Preview
Next time preview
The second store
Two Niigata Ruica's in a row.
Cool.
Niigata Louiqa and takikomi gohan is never
Oh man, it's already delicious!
Delicious!
First of all, get steak!
Two in a row!
Shumai.
Shumai!
What should I do with it?
I'll take the cheese.
Let's get the cheese from the mussels.
I'll get the steak.
That's not fair.
Wow, I want a cutlet.
I'm gonna go ask my uncle for a cutlet.
I've got two Niigata Louiqas in a row.
That's cool.
Can you get it around here?
Here.
It's some kind of cheese forging.
Thank you very much.
A pot.
It's so luxurious!
Looks delicious.
I'll take this one too.
This one too.
Excuse me.
Okay, is everyone done with their shots?
Yes, we're done.
Shall we eat now?
Yuji, do your usual.
Okay, everyone.
You two are traveling.
We're on location.
We enjoyed our time together.
And now, everyone, with all our hearts
Enjoy your meal.
Seino
Kirakira kanpai!
Cheers!
Bye-bye!
It's a rule. Kirakira kanpai is.
Well, I'll have some.
There are too many things I'm interested in, each of them.
I wanted to take a picture of that one, too.
May I have a word, first?
It's chawanmushi (steamed egg custard).
Bon appétit.
Oishii!
It's delicious.
It's so delicious.
The aroma is different.The aroma is different.
It has chicken.
Delicious.
This is a cream sauce for the prix fixe.
Please try it.
Isn't it a coincidence that our time of the year is the Purif Fair?
Yes, it is.
Bon appétit.
That's the one I recommend.
Hot!
Hot?
But it's still hot.
It's delicious.
Amazing!
Truffles?
The truffles are really mooing in my nose.
It's spreading.
Delicious.
It's great!
It's really spreading. Truffles.
You should try it, too.
It's the best.
Let's spread it out.
It's delicious.
Yongenton-don?
I put truffle sauce on it. I'm going to eat.
Bon appétit!
I'm going home.
Oh, man! The meat is so tender!
You can bite through it!
That's for sure!
Great! Oh, man!
Looks so good!
Okay, I'll go with
Firefly squid!
I really wanted to get that!
But I couldn't find it anymore.
Firefly squid, then.
Get on it! It's so good!
I can't get it!
Bon appétit! It's absolutely delicious!
Damn!
It's not just a thing. This firefly squid is amazing.
It was really spicy.
Tasty?
How do you think this firefly squid grew up?
This one has received so much love.
A firefly squid that has received a lot of love.
It has a very strong taste.
It's amazing, it's like it's on its way.
A firefly squid that has been nurtured with love.
It's the result of bees crystallizing.
It's not just about putting love on it, you know. There are a lot of them.
That's right.
Shall we eat then?
Bon appétit.
Let's eat tempura.
Me too.
Let's go, Kobomi.
It's like spring. All the winners.
When you eat tempura of wild vegetables, you feel the season, don't you?
But maybe it's not bitter at all.
It's delicious. It's refreshing.
I feel like a truffle too.
Freshly fried. They're so soft and juicy.
Shrimp.
Is it bad? It's like pudding.
The shrimp is really amazing.
Spring, there's some rice.
May I? Please have some.
Shall we use salt?
The worms are so bad.
Let's eat the worms.
They're so soft and juicy.
Delicious.
She's a little too good.
It's spring.
This sweetness in spring. I feel the season.
At first, it's pudding.
It's the warm season.The warmer weather is here.
Eh, wow!
Challenge!
It's the best!
Speaking of gero, there are hot springs!
Haruto spent a lot on footbaths earlier, and there are plenty of footbath areas that are free and open to everyone, so your skin will be smooth and smooth.
I wonder if he is still enjoying it?
I saw a lot of egret silhouettes in Gero,
Tell them why!
They say that the egrets used to get better by using the hot springs in Gero.
Is that right?
That's the history, isn't it, Mr. Cho?
Am I right?
That's amazing.
That's right.
So we are egrets?
Let's hurt each other, later.
Hurt each other?
We hurt each other.
I'm going to take care of you later,
You can't film it.
I won't tell the chief.
I can't.
I want to hear.
What's with this guy? He's talking all the time.
I don't know.
I'm giving him time to talk about asking you a question.
That's right.
Ask questions, and do it right.
Excuse me.
My apologies.
I'll try again.
What are the characteristics of the hot springs?
Please tell me the opposite.
Please.
The hot water at Gero Naga Nagaraku Honkan is alkaline simple hot spring,
After bathing in it, your skin will feel smooth,
I knew it.
Everyone says so.
I heard that the water is mild and smooth,
I don't have the concept of a mild hot spring in my mind.
That's why,
It was fresh.
I am about to experience it for the first time today.
I am looking forward to it.
You mean you will become a beautiful woman if you enter here, right?
Yes, that's right.
Let's do the vomit.
Thank you very much.
I heard what you said.
You can't film it.
It's a definite line.
That part is for sure.
I'm looking forward to it.
Definitely.
Seriously?
It's not good.
You're all alone.
This is bad.
Wait.
What a surprise.
How much of the script did you tell yourself?
I wanted to say it as soon as possible.
I'm desperate.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get it out before I forget.
Yes.
There are various facilities and spaces here,
I'm sure you'll find a lot of space here,
This is a manga corner,
This is a manga corner.
Yes.
Good, good, good.
Akimoto-san, you're getting excited,
Do you want to take a look?
Yes, let's take a look.
Let's take a look.Let's take a look.
Let's see what kind of manga you can find.
Let's take a look.
Akimoto-san, first.
May I?
There is a major one.
Let's follow Honachan.
There's Honan-kun.
Let's continue.
Honan-kun, please take a look.
Please look at Honan-kun.
This is a solo corner.
There is also a one-piece.
Good, good, good.
And then..,
Here we have,
Blues,
Rookies,
Oh.
They're coming this way.
This way.
We even have shoujo manga.
Take this,
You can read it here at your leisure.
I love Rion.
I'm a little curious.
Various things.
Oh, wow.
Yes, there is a karaoke room here.
And what's more, it's free until 7 pm.
That's right. Free of charge.
Of course we have karaoke, but we also have ping-pong, footbaths, and various other facilities.
There it is.
Great.
Until 7:00 p.m.
I'm leaving in an hour.
I can go.
Then let's sing.
Thank you for your hard work.
Next time notice
No technique at all.
Wait a minute.
Fifth place, huh?
I'm in 5th place.
Why?
I guess that means I have to work harder.
Oh, that was so much fun!
I had a great time!
I'm having a great time!
Delicious, fun and healing
It's great!
Look at the view.
The night view.
It's enchanting.
I've heard everyone say that.
The night view.
are right in front of my eyes.
It's really
It's a nice place.
It's a really nice place to stay.
We'll see you from here.
I have a day off, though.
There is a holiday, though.
Until then, I've been enjoying myself too much.
I've got another one tomorrow.
I don't really want to sleep.
But it's for tomorrow.
Right.
All of us.
Let's go to bed.
Thank you for watching.
Seino.
Good night.
It's time for Orca News.
I would like to share with you our latest news.
We are releasing our second EP on June 28th.
That's fast, bass fast. The best.
It's really early. We are very enthusiastic about this EP as Team Shachi,
This EP was made by Kenta Matsuguma.
Isn't that especially exciting in the spring?
Yes, it really is.That's right, really.
I have been listening to a lot of Matsukuma's music,
I never thought I would be able to sing his songs,
I thought it would be a great thing to do.
I'm so excited that I'm going to make an EP of your music.
That's right.
Songs that are different from mine.
It's amazing.
I think the songs will be delivered to everyone in celebration,
It has a strong message, and I think it's a song that really resonates as a song.
I hope many of you will come to the concert on June 28th, and we will also start our free live tour this weekend,
I hope many of you will come to our free live tour starting this weekend. I hope many of you will come.
And also, we are going to have a one-man live performance in Tokyo as "Shachifre", a collaboration unit of Coming Flavor and Team Shachihachi.
We will have a one-man live performance as "Shachifre" on May 18 at Blaze, Shinjuku, Tokyo.
Yay!
It is coming up this month.
Of course, we will be performing our collaboration song,
I hope we can do various things, such as live parts and collaborations,
I hope we can do various things,
If you are interested in this event, please come and join us.
We look forward to seeing you there.
And on July 22nd, we will be holding the Orca Saba at Nagoya Castle.
Yay!
A big event. It's a really important summer event for us,
And it will be held in the place where we were born,
As I said before, we will also play Matsukuma's music.
We will do it. We will definitely do it.
We will definitely do it,
We will be very happy if you dance with all your might and cheer for us with your passion,
Let's have fun together.
Let's have fun. We are waiting for you.
That's all for now.